[{"answer": "That was my CD.  Don't you ever touch a Chinese man's CD", "docId": "rush_hour_2.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Those girls drove off because of you", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Chin, you have been ordered by the that place to assist the that place and that place with our investigation, to provide us with whatever we need.  If you have information, it belongs to us", "docId": "rush_hour_2.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Two Americans have been killed on that place Government property", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Where are you going", "docId": "rush_hour_2.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Fine.  Go home.  Who needs you", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I don't want to play games with you, my friend.  I like you.  I can see myself with you", "docId": "rush_hour_2.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Called?  What's my ship called?  Well...it's called the that place", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Who", "docId": "rush_hour_2.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Nobody understands the words that are coming out of your mouth", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "No.  She's a school teacher", "docId": "rush_hour_2.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Good at what", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You thought the", "docId": "rush_hour_2.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "IT IS CRAZY", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I thought you'd think it was crazy", "docId": "rush_hour_2.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I know.  I know.  I am sorry", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I should go back.  my friend mentioned a boat in that place..", "docId": "rush_hour_2.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Follow the Rich White Man", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Slow down, baby", "docId": "rush_hour_2.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Nothing.  I said nothing", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Pick it up", "docId": "rush_hour_2.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I don't need a turn", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Master Ching taught me", "docId": "rush_hour_2.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No.  my friend's, in that place", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "One of my regulars lost fifty thousand dollars at the table here last week.  I was about to send my boys down to tune his ass up, when the guy comes in and pays off the whole thing.  Including the vig", "docId": "rush_hour_2.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I still have my lunch money from third grade", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I'm about to be killed and you", "docId": "rush_hour_2.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "It doesn't matter", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Yes.  We have heaven", "docId": "rush_hour_2.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "What's a Chinese heaven", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Mind your own business", "docId": "rush_hour_2.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "There was no sex.  She was very traditional.  We were waiting until we were married", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "There was no sex.  She was very traditional.  We were waiting until we were married", "docId": "rush_hour_2.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No m", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Who's my friend", "docId": "rush_hour_2.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "A Chinese man discovered electricity", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "my friend, he discovered electricity", "docId": "rush_hour_2.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "No Chinese man discovered electricity", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Why didn't you tell me you had a bomb in your mouth", "docId": "rush_hour_2.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "No you didn't", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "rush_hour_2.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I guess so.  Thank you, my friend", "qsentId": 42}]